Tell me a little about your day day by day
.   I'll
explain it to you.  Yes, let's take my
title which is a bit complicated.  I am
president of AI.  Head of is the part of
my job where I try to think
more long-term.  Instead, my
most everyday role, which still takes up
many hours of my day, is that of
president.  I work together with Amjad
from the CO of Replit.  We split the
responsibilities, let's say, 50 and 50. Everything
technical reports to me, the
engineering team, data, security and
obviously the whole team built
when I came here.  Then it has a few other
features that report back to me that
I'm really interested in, support,
community, devrel, basically any
team that can give me insights into
what's working and what's not
working about the product.  Exact.  About
customers.  And then another thing I
care a lot about is the team of people, of HR,
of talent.  It brings me back because
part of having a successful company,
especially in this period of NI where
everyone has to work hard and you have to
be really super skilled, is
to attract the best talent
possible.  20% of my week is
making phone calls with candidates, whether I
want to hire, so maybe they're the
first call, that is, people I
want, as they say in English,
closing, so I want to be sure they're
convinced to come,
because you have names in mind of
people who aren't here yet that
you'd like to attract.  Maybe I know them,
they work at other startups at the moment or
have done some cool projects that I know
would be a good fit for the company.
Maybe I'll start courting them.